漫威漫画
八十块了  除非你想赌翻天覆地
That's $80. Unless you want to go double or nothing.
-你在忽悠我吗  老大爷  -你说呢
- You hustling me, grandpa? - You tell me.
你知道吗  神父
Did you know, Father?
马修  你怎么来了
Matthew? What are you doing here?
你知道她是我母亲吗
Did you know she was my mother?
嗯
Yeah.
你知道
You knew.
我不能告诉你
I couldn't tell you.
即便我想说
Even when I wanted to.
别拿你的职业当挡箭牌  神父
Don't hide behind your collar, Father.
-等等  你是神父  -拿你的钱走人吧
- Wait. You're a priest? - Take your money and go.
我没想躲  马修
I'm not hiding, Matthew.
-我就在这儿  -你
- I'm right here. - You...
偏偏是你...
of all people...
我曾那么多次去向你寻求指引
All those times I looked to you for guidance.
你看着我挣扎
You saw me struggling...
却偏偏要隐瞒那一件
and you chose to hide the one thing
可以改变我一切的事
that could have changed everything for me.
拜托  神父  让我理解一下你为什么要那么做
Please, Father, help me understand why you would do that.
我多年前就祈祷玛姬能找到力量
I prayed for Maggie to find it in herself
自己告诉你
to tell you years ago.
她都没有力量
She couldn't find it in herself
走九个街区  去看孩提时的我
to walk nine blocks to visit me as a kid.
或是去安慰我  当我父亲
Or to comfort me when my father
被人杀死  而我以为...
was murdered and I thought that...
我知道自己孤身一人的时候
I knew that I was alone in this world.
-你从未孤独...  -我就是
- You were never alone-- - Yes, I was!
你让我相信就是这样了
And you let me believe it.
是的  我们那么做了
Yes. Yes, we did.
为什么
Why?
-玛姬怎么说的  -我在问你
- What did Maggie say? - I'm asking you.
玛姬是个好人  马修
Maggie's a good person, Matthew.
虽然跟每个人一样都有缺陷
Flawed, like us all.
也为她曾经的决定而备受煎熬
And tortured over decisions she's made.
但她将她的一生都用来做弥补
But she dedicated her life to making amends.
你还是没回答我的问题
You still haven't answered the question.
你从小没有父母  马修
Growing up without your parents, Matthew,
因此不再把他们看作常人了
you don't grow to see them as people.
你得去理解这一点
You need to understand that...
理解她
to understand her.
-我们走吧  就不该来  -就是啊
- We should go. This was a stupid idea. - Definitely.
我们都来了  看看的嘛
No, we're here. Let's just give it a minute.
再过三周  我们就哪都不能去了
Three weeks from now, we're not going anywhere anymore.
-是啊  -就待一分钟
- True. - Just a minute.
我吗
Me?
嗯  你  能帮个忙吗
Yeah, you. Can you give me a hand up here?
-不能  -你必须帮我
- No, I can't. - Yeah, you got to.
拜托了  我不消
Come on, it's only gonna
一分钟就能放倒那混蛋
take me 60 seconds to put this asshole down.
至多三分钟
Three minutes, tops.
-现在真该走了  -是啊  我们走吧
- Okay, now is a good time to leave. - Yes, it is. Let's go.
你要我做什么
What do you need me to do?
没什么难的
Nothing much.
就给我点水  擦擦我的脸什么的
Just gotta give me some water, maybe wipe off my face, like that.
来吧
Come on.
玛姬  服从  清贫
Maggie, obedience, poverty...
贞洁
Chastity.
你做过吗  你家里有兄弟吗
You ever done this before? You got brothers or something?
没有  都没见过人打架
No. Never seen a fight before, either.
我去
Shit.
那你为什么挑我上来
Then why'd you pick me to come up here?
我是觉得修女不会给我的瓶子里下药
I just figured a nun wouldn't put something in my bottle.
没事的
It's gonna be all right.
你只需要在一局开始时
You just gotta put my mouth guard
把护口器塞进我嘴里
in my teeth at the start of the rounds.
或许间歇时再给我喂点水
Maybe give me some water between rounds, too.
不是说只要一分钟吗
I thought you said you only needed 60 seconds.
是啊  这是备用计划  没准呢
Yeah. Well, it's just a backup plan. You never know.
水
Water.
来吧  我只有一分钟
Yeah, come on. I only got a minute.
-能擦一下吗  -那个吗
- Can you get that? - Get that?
-嗯  -好
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
玛姬  你怎么了
Maggie, what is wrong with you?
玛姬
Maggie?
Maggie.
玛姬
该死  我不知道我还能怎么办
Damn, I don't know what I should've done.
或许这么说也不对
I guess that's not really true.
当我听到玛姬喊我她的儿子时
You know, when I heard Maggie call me her son,
我想...我的第一个想法是
my thought was... my first thought...
我真是好蠢
was how stupid I'd been.
这么久以来  事实就在我眼前
That it had been right in front of me for so long.
然后我记起
And then I remembered that
事实在你眼前摆了更久
it had been in front of you for even longer.
从一开始你就知道
From-- From the beginning.
我们那么多次谈过真相
We've talked so much about truth...
你和我
you and I.
我的真相  上帝的真相
Of my truth, God's truth.
现在看来
Now it seems like
那些对话都是谎言
all those conversations were just a goddamned lie.
你真可耻
Shame on you.
不能在办公室说吗
We couldn't do this at the office?
还非得到这儿来
We had to come all the way out here?
等我向你和主管特工解释清楚了一切
Once I explain everything to you and the SAC,
您就会理解了  长官
you'll understand, sir.
那最好
Shit, I better.
-抱歉了  老大  -进来吧  两位
- Sorry about this, boss. - Come in, guys.
妈妈
Mom?
-你放哪了  -稍等我一下
- Where did you put them? - Give me a sec?
你反正也不理解
Like you'd understand.
我理解  艾莉森  但我不在乎  走吧
I understand, Allison. I just don't care. Now, move it.
一定让你爸爸把文件签了
Make sure your dad signs those papers.
我知道  再见  妈妈
I know. I know. Bye, Mom.
至少她还跟你说话呢
At least she talks to you.
我的女儿们都死盯手机不肯抬头
I can't pry my girls away from their phones.
这还是坏事吗
You say that like it's a bad thing.
抱歉这么乱
Sorry about the mess.
我的承包商保证的是几个月前就能完工
My contractor promised he would be done months ago.
-你喝什么  -黑咖啡就行  谢谢
- How do you take it? - Black is fine, thanks.
我不要
Uh, none for me.
谢谢
Thanks.
与特别探员雷胡·纳迪姆
Interview with Special Agent Rahul Nadeem
和主管特工塔米·哈特利会谈
and Special Agent in Charge Tammy Hattley,
会谈主导人  温恩特工督察
conducted by Supervisory Special Agent Winn,
联调局职业责任办公室
FBI Office of Professional Responsibility.
好了  雷  我们都在听了
Okay, Ray. You've got our attention.
你说吧
What's this about?
我没法说得委婉些
There's no good way for me to say this.
但我相信威尔逊·菲斯克
But I believe Wilson Fisk
正在进行犯罪阴谋
is currently engaged in a criminal conspiracy
而且还操纵了联调局
and has manipulated the bureau
成为了他的不知情共犯
into becoming his unwitting accomplice.
我还有理由相信
I also have reason to believe
菲斯克腐化了一名他的安保探员
that Fisk has corrupted an agent on his detail.
谁
Who?
德克斯
Dex.
你是指本·波因德克斯特特别探员吗
You're referring to Special Agent Ben Poindexter?
是的  长官  虽然听上去很疯狂
Yes, sir. And as crazy as it sounds,
我认为波因德克斯特可能是
I think Poindexter may have
公报遭袭的案犯
perpetrated the attack at the Bulletin.
你说什么呢  你为什么会那么想
What the hell are you talking about? Why would you think that?
因为我昨天根据我的怀疑进行追查时
Because while I was pursuing those suspicions yesterday...
德克斯打中了我
Dex shot me.
天呐
Jesus Christ.
长官  职责办得展开针对菲斯克的内部调查
Sir, OPR needs to start an internal investigation into Fisk,
还有波因德克斯特  这一切
into Poindexter, into all of it.
另外
And for the record...
这是我的责任
this was on my watch.
是我负责了菲斯克的安保
I personally ran Fisk's detail.
主管特工哈特利是完全照章办事
SAC Hattley did everything by the book,
这事不该影响到她
and this shouldn't fall on her.
我承担全责
I take full responsibility.
雷  抱歉  但我要让你休行政假
Ray, I'm sorry, but I'm placing you on administrative leave,
即刻生效
effective immediately.
我理解
I understand.
我会全力配合的
And will cooperate fully.
那么
So...
接下来怎么办
what do we do next?
首先  我们给你叫辆救护车
First, we call you an ambulance.
不
No!
雷  把枪放下  求你
Ray! Put down the gun! Please!
该死  雷  你把这带到我家来
Damn you, Ray. You bring this into my house?
我家
My home?
坐下
Sit down.
坐
Sit.
你的指纹  你的武器  还有录音
Your prints, your weapon, the recording.
需要我给你解释这意味着什么吗
Do I need to explain to you what this means?
请回答问题  你明白现在的情况吗
Answer my question, please. Do you understand your situation now?
雷
Ray?
你明白吗
You get this?
是的  老大
Yeah, boss.
我明白了
I understand.
我不是你的老大了
I'm not your boss anymore.
威尔逊·菲斯克才是
Wilson Fisk is.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     夜魔草
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     纸袋
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
夜
魔
侠
第三季  第九集
你不用跑的  躲起来也可以
You don't have to run. Hiding is an option.
那恐怕不行  福吉  我对菲斯克撂了狠话
I'm not so sure it is, Foggy. Not after what I said to Fisk.
-你要去哪  -我不知道
- Where will you go? - I don't know.
但我不会像之前为马特那样付房租了
But I wouldn't bother paying the rent like we did for Matt.
拜托  你会回来的
Come on. You'll be back.
福吉  菲斯克会一直追杀我的
Foggy, Fisk is never gonna stop hunting me.
那就别跑别躲  像我那样
Then don't run or hide. Do what I did.
曝光自己  让他不能动你
Make yourself so public he can't touch you.
那是没用的  福吉
Yeah, well, it's not gonna matter, Foggy.
我的地检官竞选就让我没有被他追杀
My DA campaign's kept me out of his crosshairs so far.
你可没承认杀了他的好闺蜜
Yeah, well, you didn't confess to killing his BFF, so...
有道理
Valid point.
-但或许  -福吉  我要跑了
- But maybe-- - Look, Foggy. I'm running.
不过我要先告诉马特我完全出卖了他
Right after I tell Matt I completely betrayed him.
得了
Come on.
你没有出卖他
You didn't betray him.
菲斯克因为我知道马特是夜魔侠了
Fisk knows that Matt is Daredevil because of me.
他不能确定的  你什么都没说
He can't actually know that for sure. You didn't say anything.
你没在场  他...
No, you weren't there. He, uh...
他看我的眼神
The way he looked at me...
他知道了
He knows.
替我销毁这个
Just, uh, destroy these for me?
-不  福吉  -拿着吧
- No, Foggy... - Please take it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我该走了
I should go.
我们能撑过去的
We're gonna get through this.
我不知道怎么撑  但能撑过去的
I don't know how, but we will.
务必小心点
Watch your back. Please.
改变是可怕的  马可斯
Change can be scary, Marcus.
哪怕是好的改变
Even when it's for the good.
才不是
No, it's not.
多克利一家非常好
You know, the Dockerys are a wonderful family,
现在你可以成为他们的一员了
and now you get to be a part of it.
但你也永远是我们的大家庭一员
But you will always be a part of our family, too.
玛姬
Maggie.
怎么了  保罗
What is it, Paul?
马修知道了
Matthew knows.
看来你都知道了  马特
I guess you know everything now, Matty.
我需要知道的一切
Everything I need to.
不  这并不能改变什么
Meh. Doesn't change a goddamn thing.
-雷  -嗯
- Ray? - Yeah?
你同事来找你
You have a visitor from work.
我的手不够大
My hand's not big enough.
怎么不够  看
Sure it is. Look.
手指这样  握住边缝
Just keep your fingers like that, hugging the seam,
丢球的时候甩手腕
and just snap your wrist when you release it.
就能投出曲线了吗
And that makes it curve?
绝对的
Like crazy.
他来了  早啊  雷
There he is. Morning, Ray.
爸爸  他在教我丢曲线球
Dad, he's teaching me how to throw a curveball.
你吃鸡蛋吗
You want eggs?
不了  谢谢
Uh, no, thanks.
-去准备上学  萨米  -但爸爸
- Go get ready for school, Sami. - But, Dad...
先去上学  孩子
School first, kid.
好吧
Okay.
这好酷  谢谢  波因德克斯特先生
This is cool. Thanks, Mr. Poindexter.
喊我德克斯就行  你爸跟我交情很深
Call me Dex. Your dad and me go way back.
德克斯  你怎么来我家了
So, Dex, what brings you to my house?
你一直吹嘘西玛的厨艺
Well, you've been bragging about Seema's cooking for so long,
我就想找个借口来尝尝看
I figured I'd come up with an excuse to finally come try it.
你不需要借口  德克斯  你对我们家的恩情
You don't need an excuse, Dex. What you've done for our family...
你永远受欢迎
...you're always welcome here.
亲爱的  我们得谈工作的事
Honey, we're gonna talk shop.
好  但别说太久
Okay. But only for a few minutes.
别让德克斯的鸡蛋放凉了
I don't want Dex's eggs getting cold.
你来干什么  德克斯
What are you doing here, Dex?
你有问题找我  别找我家人
Your issue is with me, not my family.
我的问题确实是你
My issue is definitely with you.
律师那套  雷  真是冷酷
That stunt with the lawyer, Ray? That was cold.
你让我以为你会罩我
You convinced me that you had my back.
但菲斯克要你活着
But Fisk wants you alive.
他要我做什么  德克斯
What does he want from me, Dex?
你的朋友  你带去我家的那个
Your friend. The one you brought to my home.
我不知道他是谁  或是他在哪
I don't know who he is. Or where he is.
你知道
Yeah, you do.
但这个不急
But it can wait.
你在流血  雷
You're bleeding, Ray.
你去换衬衫  我在西玛这儿替你打掩护
I'll cover with Seema while you change your shirt.
走吧  我们今天要一起玩  搭档
Now, let's go. We're spending the day together, partner.
好香啊
It smells delicious.
味道也那么好吗
Taste as good as it looks?
该死
Shit.
楼管会修的
I have a super for that.
我能修好的
I can fix this, damn it.
-你没事吧  -好极了
- You okay? - Peachy.
凯伦和马特想怎么随他们  我才不跑
Karen and Matt can do whatever they want. I'm not gonna run.
你现在不能停止  你给了大家希望
You can't quit now. You're giving people hope.
沃布肖太太在农产品摊位前拦下了我
Mrs. Wobschall stopped me in the produce aisle.
起初我还不信
At first, I didn't believe her,
但她用手机给我看了视频
but then she showed me a clip on her iPhone.
你真是天生的  太棒了
You were a natural. Totally amazing.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
因为当你超越冰冷的事实
Because when you get beyond the cold facts,
对你所做的事真正激动起来  你就能...
and you really get worked up about what you're doing, you can...
糟糕
Holy shit.
显然  结语还需要练习
Clearly, we've got to work on your closing,
但视频头24小时里已经有
but this video has had nearly 100,000
超过10万点击量了
views in its first 24 hours.
纽约半数警察
Half the cops in New York
都在自己的账号上转发了
have reposted it to their personal accounts.
布雷克·陶瓦回应了吗
Has Blake Tower responded?
完全静默
Complete radio silence.
应该是因为你成功把他竖立成了
Probably because you've successfully branded him
支持菲斯克的候选人
as the pro-Fisk candidate
而他再说什么之会火上浇油
and anything he says will only make it worse.
福吉  如果你做得好
Foggy, if you play this right...
我还真能赢
I could actually win.
作为新地检
And as the new DA,
你的第一要务
you make it your top priority
就是扳倒威尔逊·菲斯克
to nail Wilson Fisk.
我没多少时间  菲斯克有动作
I don't have much time. Fisk is doing something.
说清楚点  雷
Specifics, Ray.
我不知道  但我知道了  就打给你
I don't know what. But when I do, I'll call you.
做好准备
Be ready.
好了
It's done.
做得好  搭档
Nice work, partner.
这样知道确实很不好  马特  你妈妈的事
It's a shitty way for you to find out, Matty, about your mother.
是啊  你该告诉我的
Yeah. You should have told me.
或许我答应了她不说的
Maybe I promised her that I wouldn't.
那不是借口
That is no excuse.
我知道  孩子
Yeah, I know, kid.
但我中枪后
But after I took that bullet,
玛姬有很多年时间告诉你  但她没有
Maggie had years to tell you the truth and she didn't.
那不是我的选择  是她的
That wasn't my choice, it was hers.
你们都撒谎了  也都离开了我
You both lied. You both left.
我没离开你
I never left you.
你没有听从吩咐在那场比赛里输掉
You didn't go down in that fight like you were supposed to.
明知他们会为此杀了你
Knowing they'd kill you for it.
我那是为了你
I did that for you.
这样你才会知道你老爸的骨气
So you'd know what your old man is made of.
我老爸选择了骄傲而不是陪儿子度过余生
My old man chose his ego over a lifetime with his son.
我只知道这个
That's what I know.
不是骄傲  是遵守准则
It wasn't ego, it was living up to a code.
做个男人
Being a man.
那就是喜欢我的拳头打在别人脸上的感觉
It means lovin' the feel of my fist in someone else's face.
就是等着他们倒在地上
It means waiting for them to hit the ground
而且知道是我打倒了他们
and knowing that I put them there.
没错
And, yeah, okay...
或许我是把这放在了第一位
maybe I put that at the top of my list and
而因此失去了一切
maybe it cost me everything,
包括你
including you.
但你也一样
But you do the same thing.
才不呢
No, I don't.
你也有准则  你把人打得半死
You have a code, too. You beat the shit out of people.
你告诉自己没关系  因为你没杀人
You tell yourself it's okay because you didn't kill anyone.
我们有毛病  马特  我们就是这样的人
There is something wrong with us, Matty. It's just who we are.
那是你  爸爸
That's who you were, Dad.
我跟你不一样
I'm not like you.
我不假输
I don't throw fights.
我也不因为扯淡的准则
And I don't let everyone else suffer
就让其他人受苦
'cause of some bullshit code.
今后不了
Not anymore.
等我找到菲斯克
When I get to Fisk...
我要杀了他
I'm gonna kill him.
-玛姬修女  -德文
- Sister Maggie... Sister Maggie? - Devin.
打扰  玛姬修女
Excuse me, Sister Maggie?
抱歉打扰你  他们说你在这儿
I'm sorry to bother you. They told me I could find you here.
他走了  我不知道去哪了
He's gone. I don't know where.
这是性命攸关的大事
It's a matter of life and death.
你知道他什么时候会回来吗
Do you have any idea when he'll be back?
他不会回来了
He won't be.
我
I...
我不懂  为什么不会
I don't understand. Why? Why not?
他发现了真相
He learned the truth.
我是他妈妈
That I'm his mother.
他从未提过...你
He never talked about... about you.
我抛弃马修时  对他有危险
I was a danger to Matthew when I gave him up.
现在  人们很了解产后抑郁了  但是
Nowadays, they know a great deal about postpartum, but...
当时
at the time...
我深信自己背叛了上帝
I was convinced that I was betraying God.
我当时尚未宣誓  但我心里
I hadn't yet taken my vows, but in my heart...
我相信我犯下了不可饶恕的罪孽
I believed I had committed an unforgivable sin.
所以我犯下了别的罪来做弥补
And so I replaced that sin with another.
我抛弃了我的孩子
I abandoned my child.
你为什么现在告诉他
Why... Why did you tell him now?
我没有  他自己发现的
I didn't. He found out on his own.
我想告诉他的
I wanted to tell him.
杰克还活着时
When Jack was alive,
我说服自己  真相只会让马修不解
I convinced myself the truth would confuse Matthew.
但杰克死后  我又说服自己
After Jack died, I convinced myself
告诉他弊大于利
it would do more harm than good.
最终  我意识到
Finally, I just realized that
我太懦弱了
I was too much of a coward.
主行事有方
The Lord has a way.
现在把地狱厨房的恶魔送来了我这儿
Sending the Devil of Hell's Kitchen to me now.
让我看到我的罪孽的恶果
Showing me what became of my sin.
主又给了我个弥补的机会
The Lord gave me another chance to make things right.
可我又失败了
And I failed, yet again.
马修现在知道我是什么人了
Matthew knows who and what I am now.
他不会回来了
He won't be back.
对不起  我不该让你背负这些事
I'm sorry. It's unfair of me to burden you.
我不...
I just... I don't...
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
你能对终生伤害了你朋友的人说什么呢
What can you say to someone who's scarred your friend for life?
他现在一定非常痛苦
He must be in a lot of pain right now.
等你找到他  他会需要个朋友的
When you find him, he'll need a friend.
问题就在这里  我不能留下了
That's just it. See, I can't really stick around.
菲斯克知道马特的事了
Fisk knows... about Matt. I just...
我只想在逃跑之前提醒他
I just wanted to warn him before I run.
-你有危险吗  -是的
- Are you in danger? - Yeah.
马特不是菲斯克唯一想杀的人
Matt's not the only one that Fisk wants dead.
你有可去的地方吗
Do you have someplace to go?
没有  我要搭最早的车出城
No, I was just gonna get the first bus out of town.
我可以帮你
I can help you.
不了  你现在最好别留我在身边
Uh, yeah, no, you don't want me anywhere near you right now.
相信我
Trust me.
教堂两千年来一直在帮助人们躲藏
The church has been helping people hide for 2,000 years.
藏在这里吧
Hide here.
给我一天时间联系联系
Give me a day to make a few calls,
到周末时
and you'll have shelter
你能在半个地球外的地方找到庇护所
halfway around the world by the end of the week.
拜托  让我帮你吧
Please, let me do something for you.
为了马修
For Matthew.
好
Yeah.
各位  我要宣布一件事
Everybody, I have an announcement.
经过这操蛋的一周终于有好消息了
And some good news after a shitty week.
我很高兴地告诉大家
I'm happy to tell you that
特别探员波因德克斯特已被复职
Special Agent Poindexter has been reinstated to duty.
就连华府也不能拿英勇事迹来一直压着人
Turns out even DC can't hold good deeds against someone forever.
说真的  各位
Seriously, people...
大家一起帮助德克斯雇了律师
the way you came together and helped Dex hire that lawyer...
我为你们骄傲
I'm proud of you.
如果我们不彼此照应  谁还会照顾我们
If we don't look out for each other, who will?
有什么想说的吗  德克斯
You got anything to say, Dex?
我只想说谢谢
I guess I just wanna say thank you.
没有你们帮忙我就回不来
I wouldn't be here without your help.
尤其是你  雷
Especially you, Ray.
我早晚要报答你为我做的一切
Someday, I'll pay you back for everything you did.
你看上去很好  富兰克林
You look good, Franklin.
我依然对法律的能力充满激情
I'm still passionate about what the law can do.
但或许下次该剪剪头
Maybe a haircut next time, though.
他这下可是出名了
He's making quite the name for himself.
西奥  来看看你哥哥的这部电影
Theo, you gotta see this movie your brother's in.
我给你弄盘吃的  亲爱的  来
Let me fix you a plate, sweetie. Come here.
等等  妈妈  我得跟福吉说句话
Hold on, Ma. I need a couple minutes with Foggy.
马上回来
I'll be quick.
别担心她  福吉  她不会有事的
Don't worry about her, Foggy. She'll be fine.
玛茜  你考虑过冷冻卵子吗
So, Marci, have you considered freezing your eggs?
-永远不算晚哦  -安娜
- It's never too late. - Anna!
最好是要紧事
This better be important.
你在视频上说的关于菲斯克的话
All that stuff you said about Fisk on the video,
你得收回来
you gotta take it back.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你得再做段视频
You have to make a different video, man.
或是发布声明  说你当时喝醉了
Issue a statement or whatever. Say you were drunk.
恰恰相反  弟弟
Au contraire, mon frère.
那绝不可以
That's the last thing I gotta do.
我得利用这个机会
I gotta exploit this opportunity
揭露菲斯克所做的一切
to expose everything Fisk is doing.
不不  福吉  听我说  你得道歉
No, no, no. Foggy, listen to me. You need to apologize.
怎么了  有人来找你了吗  西奥
What happened? Did someone come after you, Theo?
福吉  情况很糟
Fog, it's real bad.
大概一年前
About a year ago,
我们的一些供货商突然不接我们的单了
some of our suppliers stopped taking our orders.
就是不干了  我完全无法理解
Just stopped. No reason I could understand.
我们怎么讲价他们都不肯回心转意
We couldn't change their minds for the love of money.
几个月后
After a few months,
店铺的财务就出现了危机
the shop was in a tight spot financially, right?
我们也没有担保物可以贷款
And we didn't have the collateral to get a loan--
你怎么不找我  我可以帮忙的
Why didn't you come to me? I could have helped.
我不需要  因为接下来发生了转机
I didn't have to, because of what happened next.
突然  我接到一个陌生银行来的电话
Out of the blue, I get this call from a bank I never heard of
说要帮助我们  红狮银行
offering to help us out. Red Lion Bank.
-该死  -你知道他们吗
- Shit. - You know these guys?
继续说
Just keep going.
信贷人员
So, the loan officer there,
他教我怎么做账
he coaches me on how to move the numbers around.
让我们的财务状况看上去更好些
Make our assets look healthier, you know.
果然  贷款顺利申请了下来
And bam! The loan comes through without a hitch.
我也没再多想  生活继续了
I don't give it another thought. Life goes on.
我们经历了不少起落
I mean, we've been through a lot around here.
以前的供货商也都回来了
And the old suppliers came back.
对  是的  说起来的话
Yeah. Yeah, they did, now you mention it.
然后有人来找你谈话
And then someone came to talk to you?
就今天下午  一个英国老头来见我
This afternoon, yeah. This old English dude comes to see me.
他知道我在贷款申请时篡改账目的事
He knew all about the creative accounting on the loan app.
他说除非我说服你
He said unless I could convince you
撤销对菲斯克的一切指控
to walk back everything you said about Fisk...
他就会让红狮收回贷款
he'd have Red Lion call the loan.
当然了
Of course.
福吉  那份申请
Foggy, that application...
如果有人仔细审视
if anyone looks too carefully at it...
你会进监狱
You're going to jail.
不止是我
Not just me.
爸爸妈妈也签字了
Mom and Dad signed it, too.
我们今天有了新队员
We have a new teammate today.
请坐吧  雷
Take a seat, Ray.
难以置信  菲斯克有你们所有人的把柄
I don't believe it. Fisk's got something on all of you?
阿里诺利
Arinori?
我们最好还是别说了
Better we don't talk about it.
在这里  我们都不提他的名字
And in here, we don't even say his name.
这是规矩之一  雷
That's one of the rules, Ray.
我们只喊他的代号
We only refer to him by his code name.
什么代号
What code name?
金并
Kingpin.
新一轮围剿  先生们
Another roundup, gentlemen.
我们要出手迅猛
And we're going to hit them fast and hard.
金并要拿这次声明立场
Kingpin wants this one to make a point.
联调局  别动
FBI! Don't move!
该死  是条子
Shit. It's the feds!
趴在地上
Down on the ground, now!
-别动  -不
- Stay where you are. - No.
约翰·哈默  你跟我们来
John Hammer, you're coming with us.
早啊  斯塔先生
Good morning, Mr. Starr.
交给我
I got this one.
请平静地随我们来
Please come quietly.
-换岗  各位  -我们一小时前才到
- Shift change, guys. - We just came on an hour ago.
哈特利的命令
Hattley's orders.
她应该是在惩罚我那么快就复职了
I think she's punishing me for getting off suspension so fast.
多谢你还捎上了我
And thanks for bringing me along for the ride.
她是老大嘛
She's the boss.
回见
See you later.
因为什么  钱吗
So what was it? Money?
我认识你十年了  天呐
I've known you for ten years, for Chrissakes.
闭上你的嘴
Shut your goddamn mouth.
怎么  你要再栽赃我一宗谋杀吗
Or what? You'll frame me for another murder?
脑袋向前
Keep your head forward.
这里没有麦  但你知道他们在看
There's no mics in here, but you know they're watching.
你杀了温恩  你怎么能安心
You murdered Winn. How do you live with that?
我杀他是为了救你
I killed him to save your life.
没错  这是因为你
That's right. This is on you.
我没叫你闯入德克斯的公寓
I didn't tell you to break into Dex's apartment.
我要知道会阻止你的  你就不会在这儿了
I would've stopped you, and you wouldn't be here.
但还是如此了
But here you are.
我不敢相信你想要这样
I can't believe you want this.
是我们造成了这一切  我们也能结束它
We made this happen. We can find a way to end it.
根本没有出路  雷
There's no way out, Ray.
菲斯克盯你一年多了
Fisk's had you marked for more than a year.
什么意思  盯我
What do you mean, had me marked?
你以为你嫂子为什么失去了医保
Why do you think your sister-in-law lost health coverage?
他让你迫不及待地想要这份工作
He made you desperate for this job,
你尽全力帮他住进了顶层公寓
you did everything you could to get him this penthouse,
满足了他的一切要求
get him everything he asked for.
就像我说的  没有出路
Like I said, there's no way out.
我们根本拼不过
We're out of our league here.
你本可以去找国土安全部或纽约警局
You could've gone to Homeland Security or the NYPD.
而不是拉我下水  杀别的探员
Not take me down with you. Not murder an agent.
你提交报告  把家人送去安全的地方  天呐
You make a report. You get your family somewhere safe. Jesus.
这对菲斯克行不通的
That's not an option with Fisk.
我以前有俩孩子  雷
I used to have two children, Ray.
他们做得像肇事逃逸
They made it look like a hit-and-run.
我离了婚  这或许能稍稍保护他
I got a divorce. Maybe that keeps him a little safer.
但我还有艾莉  所以
But there's still Allie, so...
想想西玛和萨米吧
Think about Seema and Sami.
照菲斯克的话做
And do what Fisk tells you.
-谢尔比太太呢  -她就来  先生
- Where is Mrs. Shelby? - She's on her way, sir.
不
No.
纳迪姆
Nadeem.
走吧
Let's go.
-喂  -菲斯克离开酒店了
- Yeah? - Fisk has left the hotel.
那怎么可能
How is that possible?
我觉得德克斯不是唯一叛变的联调局探员
I don't think Dex was the only FBI agent he turned.
但他要带菲斯克去见其他犯罪头目
But he's taking Fisk to meet with other crime bosses.
-要谈什么事  -在哪
- Some kind of sit-down. - Where?
我把地址发短信给你
I'm texting you the address.
但如果你能抓菲斯克个正着
But if you catch Fisk in the act--
这是我们扳倒他的机会  谢谢  纳迪姆
This is our chance to take him down. Thank you, Nadeem.
我们里面见  纳迪姆
We'll meet you inside, Nadeem.
你要我做什么
What do you want me to do?
做好准备
Be ready.
夜魔侠会知道这是陷阱  但他还是会来
Daredevil will know it's a trap, but he'll come anyway.
红鱼蓝餐馆
Red Fish Blue Restaurant,
48街和九大道
48th Street and 9th Avenue.
你不会上当吧
You're not fallin' for that, are you?
那人  他已经不是你这边的了
That guy, he ain't in your corner. Not anymore.
无所谓
That doesn't matter.
你很久没用过泰拳绳了
It's been a long time since you used Muay Thai ropes, Matty.
那个穿我战衣的家伙揍扁了我
That guy in my suit kicked my ass.
我远距离打不过他
I can't beat him from a distance.
我得引他靠近  才能伤他更深
I gotta draw him in close and do more damage.
你太气愤  脑袋不清醒  你会送命的
You're too mad to think straight. And it's gonna get you killed.
马特  得了
Matty, come on.
你妈妈不仅是离开了你  她也离开了我
Your mother didn't only leave you. She left me, too.
你想寻求同情吗  别指望了
You looking for sympathy? 'Cause that's not happening.
她离开我们  因为我们被诅咒了
She left us because we're cursed.
因为她知道我们体内有恶魔
Because she knew we got the devil inside.
那怪我咯
So it's my fault?
你能不能别再自欺欺人了
Would you be honest with yourself?
你戴上那面具
You put on that mask
是因为它让你接受真正的你
because it lets you feel all right with who you really are.
它让你伤害别人
It lets you hurt people
还让你觉得那是为了重要的原因
and makes you feel like it's for something important...
好的原因  甚至是为了上帝
...something good, maybe even for God.
但那不是真相  我们都清楚
But that ain't the truth, and we both know it.
你和你父亲是一个模子印出来的
You and your father are cut from the same cloth.
受贿拳击手  施加痛苦给他的满足感
A corrupt boxer who takes as much satisfaction in inflicting pain
就像拿钱假输一样强烈
as he does money for taking dives.
他的儿子
And his son,
想说服自己
who's trying to convince himself
他比他的罪犯老爸要好
he's any better than his criminal father.
你们生来一无是处
You were born from nothing.
你们永远一无是处
You remain nothing.
-逮捕我  否则我就走了  -别动
- Arrest me, or I'm leaving. - Stay where you are.
我们有权请律师
We have a right to counsel.
这太扯了  我们还等什么
This some bullshit. What are we waiting for?
时候到了我们自会知道
We'll know when it happens.
你知道现在是什么情况吗
You know something about what's going on?
他们低调地抓我们过来
Well, they pick us up all quiet like.
没有媒体  不拉去游街
No press, no perp walk.
带我们来这儿而不是市区  联调局有所求
Take us here instead of downtown. The feds want something.
-菲斯克  -这是怎么回事
- Fisk? - What the hell is this?
是个机会  斯塔先生
It's an opportunity, Mr. Starr.
我叫你们来  是想给你们提供保护
I've brought you here to offer you my protection.
免遭联邦政府的调查和检控
From investigations and prosecutions by the federal government.
扯淡  这是钓鱼执法
Bullshit. This is a sting.
陪审团  如果你们在录音带上听到
Hey, jury, if you can hear this on tape,
我是无辜的
I'm totally innocent.
我都不认识这些人
I don't even know these people.
多少钱  有什么条件
How much? What's the vig?
-20%  -天呐
- Twenty percent. - For Chrissake.
全部收入的两成
Of everything.
你带着那么多臭狗屎
I don't know how you keep that
是怎么保持那身西装洁白无瑕的
suit white with all the bullshit you pack into it.
我知道这怎么回事  我们都知道
I know what this is. We all know what this is.
你想骗我们招供  好再在你靠花招换来的
You want us to confess to something that buys you another month
酒店房间里多待一个月
in that hotel suite you conned yourself into.
不  我不干
No. You can count me out.
提成现在是25%了
The tax is now 25 percent.
我真得承认  菲斯克  你太会作秀了
I gotta hand it to you, Fisk. You know how to put on a show.
就一个问题  我去哪送钱
Just one question. Where do I drop the cash?
如果你提示了他
If you tipped him...
我完全照你的要求说的
I said exactly what you told me to say.
你也在场
You were there.
走吧
Let's go.
前往楼梯井C  拿出武器
Moving to Stairwell C. Weapons out.
你要杀我吗
Are you gonna kill me?
不
No.
不是你
Not you.
菲斯克
Fisk?
无信号
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
他什么时候回来
When will he be back?
几分钟内
Minutes.
谢谢
Thank you.
凯伦·佩吉被发现在克林顿教堂
Karen Page located at the Clinton Church.
让所有纽约警局警员
Keep all NYPD units
远离那里  除非另行通知  收到吗
clear of that location until otherwise advised. Copy?
菲斯克要把凯伦怎么样
What does Fisk want with Karen?
他要她死
He wants her killed.